<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Better BibTeX for Zotero</title>
    <link>/zotero-better-bibtex/index.html</link>
    <description>Make Zotero more useful for us LaTeX holdouts</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <atom:link href="/zotero-better-bibtex/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Installation</title>
      <link>/zotero-better-bibtex/installation/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/zotero-better-bibtex/installation/index.html</guid>
      <description>Install by downloading the latest release – if you use Firefox, make sure to right-click and save the XPI file, not just clicking it – and then in Zotero:&#xA;In the main menu go to Tools &gt; Add-ons Select ‘Plugins’ Click on the gear in the top-right corner and choose ‘Install Add-on From File…’ Choose .xpi that you’ve just downloaded, click ‘Install’ If you’re using Zotero 6, restart Zotero. Installation in Zotero 7 requires no restart. After the initial installation, the plugin will auto-update to newer releases, so you should need to perform the process described here only once.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exporting items</title>
      <link>/zotero-better-bibtex/exporting/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/zotero-better-bibtex/exporting/index.html</guid>
      <description>Better BibTex adds a couple of export formats to Zotero’s export dialog and several ways to improve export for plaintext-based authoring. The Better BibTeX configuration pane can be found under the regular Zotero preferences pane, tab ‘Better BibTeX’ where you can tweak the exports, such as&#xA;Omitting fields from exports to slim down your bib files. Configuring how citation keys are generated. And really a ton more. Additionally you can automate exporting (parts of) your library either using auto-export or pull export.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Citation Keys</title>
      <link>/zotero-better-bibtex/citing/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/zotero-better-bibtex/citing/index.html</guid>
      <description>Generating citekeys for your items The BibTeX citations keys generated by the standard Zotero exporters are always generated at time of export, using an algorithm that usually generates unique keys. For serious LaTeX users, “usually” presents the following problems:&#xA;If a non-unique key is generated, which one gets postfixed with a distinguishing character is essentially non-deterministic. The keys are always auto-generated, so if you correct a typo in the author name or title, the key will change You can’t see the citation keys until you export them For a LaTeX author, the citation keys have their own meaning, fully separate from the other entry data, even if people usually pick a naming scheme related to them. As the citation key is the piece of data that connects your bibliography, this is a piece of data you want to have control over. BBT offers you this control:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Support</title>
      <link>/zotero-better-bibtex/support/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/zotero-better-bibtex/support/index.html</guid>
      <description>Before all else, thank you for taking the time for submitting an issue, and I’m sorry that I’ve probably interrupted your flow.&#xA;Your report matters to me. I love hearing my software helps you, and it pains me to know that things aren’t working for you.&#xA;If you have any questions on the use of the plugin, please do not hesitate to file a GitHub issue to ask for help.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sponsoring BBT</title>
      <link>/zotero-better-bibtex/sponsoring/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/zotero-better-bibtex/sponsoring/index.html</guid>
      <description>While the development needs of BBT are to a large extent covered by the generosity towards open-source developers of services such as github, my development system does require the occasional upgrade; also, I enjoy getting the occasional frivolous tech-toy that I wouldn’t otherwise grant myself. While you should feel in no way obligated to pay for BBT, anything you can spare is very much appreciated. If you’d rather contribute a little bit each month (and a little means a lot) so I can save up for a replacement a year or so down the line, head on over to Patreon, but mind that Patreon takes a fairly large cut of what you give.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>