<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Configuration on Better BibTeX for Zotero</title>
    <link>/better-bibtex/configuration/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Configuration on Better BibTeX for Zotero</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    
	<atom:link href="/better-bibtex/configuration/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Citation keys</title>
      <link>/better-bibtex/configuration/citation-keys/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/better-bibtex/configuration/citation-keys/</guid>
      <description>Citation key format default: ​[auth:lower][shorttitle3_3][year]
Set the pattern used to generate citation keys. The format of the keys is documented here.
Force citation key to plain text default: True
If you have deviated from the default citation key format pattern by specifying your own, you may wind up with non-ASCII characters in your citation keys. You can prevent that using the fold function at the appropriate place in your pattern, but checking this checkbox will just apply fold to all your keys.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Export</title>
      <link>/better-bibtex/configuration/export/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/better-bibtex/configuration/export/</guid>
      <description>Export unicode as plain-text latex commands (recommended) default: True
* BibTeX has really spotty Unicode support, so you generally want this on. It will translate things like accented characters to their equivalent LaTeX constructs on export.
Disregard name prefixes when sorting default: False
* Name handling is a lot more complex than I had ever thought it to be. A lot more complex. BibTeX has really limited ways of dealing with names with particles (van, von, de, etc).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Automatic export</title>
      <link>/better-bibtex/configuration/automatic-export/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/better-bibtex/configuration/automatic-export/</guid>
      <description>Automatic export default: On Change
Determines when automatic exports are kicked off. Having it disabled still marks auto-exports as needing updates, so when you re-enable it, those exports will start. On-change means exports happen whenever a reference in the export changes/is added/is removed. On idle does more or less what Disabled (that is, no exports but mark as needing changes), but will kick off exports when your computer is idle.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advanced</title>
      <link>/better-bibtex/configuration/advanced/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/better-bibtex/configuration/advanced/</guid>
      <description>Deterministically order references and fields; primarily for version control. default: False
When on, BBT will deterministically order references on export. This is primarily interesting if you keep the exported file under some kind of version control. Comes at performance and memory consumption cost.
postscript default: &amp;lt;not set&amp;gt;
Snippet of javascript to run after each reference generation.
@string definitions default: &amp;lt;not set&amp;gt;
If you have externally maintained @string vars paste them here and they will be resolved for subsequent imports</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hidden preferences</title>
      <link>/better-bibtex/configuration/hidden-preferences/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/better-bibtex/configuration/hidden-preferences/</guid>
      <description>The following settings are not exposed in the UI, but can be found under Preferences/Advanced/Config editor.
All are prefixed with extensions.zotero.translators.better-bibtex. in the table you will find there
ascii default: &amp;lt;not set&amp;gt;
If you have unicode turned on you can still selectively replace some characters to plain-text commands; any characters entered here will always be replaced by their LaTeX-command counterparts.
autoExportIdleWait default: 10
Number of seconds to wait after your system goes idle before kicking off auto-exports.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>