<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Support on Better BibTeX for Zotero</title>
    <link>/support/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Support on Better BibTeX for Zotero</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    
	<atom:link href="/support/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Frequently Asked Questions</title>
      <link>/support/faq/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/support/faq/</guid>
      <description>Are there any plans to support Firefox 57+? BBT lives where Zotero lives, and Zotero only has standalone these days. BBT is installed inside Zotero instead of in the browser. Please see the installation instructions to get started with BBT.
BBT is changing the capitalization of my titles &amp;ndash; why? There isn&amp;rsquo;t a straightforward one-to-one mapping for all Zotero to Bib(La)TeX fields. For most I can make reasonable choices, but there are some things where Better BibTeX takes a little more liberties with your references in order to get sensible output.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Performance</title>
      <link>/support/performance/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/support/performance/</guid>
      <description>The Better BibTeX exporters are a lot slower than the standard Zotero Bib(La)TeX exporters. If you have a small library, you will not likely notice this, but if you have several thousand references, and you are in the habit of exporting substantial parts of your library, this gets annoying really fast.
To deal with this problem, Better BibTeX implements an extensive caching system. With a filled cache, Better BibTeX is substantially faster than the default Zotero exporters.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Translations</title>
      <link>/support/translations/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/support/translations/</guid>
      <description>BBT is currently available in English, German and French. You can help out by adding new translations or fixing existing ones on Crowdin.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>