<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Citation Keys :: Better BibTeX for Zotero</title>
    <link>/zotero-better-bibtex/citing/index.html</link>
    <description>Generating citekeys for your items The BibTeX citations keys generated by the standard Zotero exporters are always generated at time of export, using an algorithm that usually generates unique keys. For serious LaTeX users, “usually” presents the following problems:&#xA;If a non-unique key is generated, which one gets postfixed with a distinguishing character is essentially non-deterministic. The keys are always auto-generated, so if you correct a typo in the author name or title, the key will change You can’t see the citation keys until you export them For a LaTeX author, the citation keys have their own meaning, fully separate from the other entry data, even if people usually pick a naming scheme related to them. As the citation key is the piece of data that connects your bibliography, this is a piece of data you want to have control over. BBT offers you this control:</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <atom:link href="/zotero-better-bibtex/citing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Cite as you Write</title>
      <link>/zotero-better-bibtex/citing/cayw/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/zotero-better-bibtex/citing/cayw/index.html</guid>
      <description>PSA: as of Zotero 5.0.71, access to the CAYW URL will no longer work from the browser for security reasons; curl and other programmatic access such as from editors access will work.&#xA;Good news for TeXnicians and those down with Mark (aka Markdown, RST, whatnot): this is the time to go pester the author of your favorite editor for Zotero integration!&#xA;Editor integration vim Graciously supplied by David Lukes:&#xA;paste it in your .vimrc (and modify to your liking):</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Migrating from Word/Libreoffice</title>
      <link>/zotero-better-bibtex/citing/migrating/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/zotero-better-bibtex/citing/migrating/index.html</guid>
      <description>So you have decided that enough is enough, and you want to migrate your existing Word/Libreoffice document to LaTeX/Markdown. Plenty (well…) tools exist to help with the migration of your document content, pandoc being the most prominent one, but one thing none of them will do is keep your citations intact. This will not do.&#xA;If you install this CSL style in Zotero (or modify it further and use that), Zotero will render the in-text citations as [@citekey] when you ask Zotero to render the bibliography. If you want LaTeX, modify the style accordingly. You can then put your document through pandoc or whatnot to get LaTeX/Markdown.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AUX Scanner</title>
      <link>/zotero-better-bibtex/citing/aux-scanner/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/zotero-better-bibtex/citing/aux-scanner/index.html</guid>
      <description>You can populate a collection, or tag items in your library, from an existing paper by scanning the aux file generated by bibtex, or a pandoc-markdown file, for referenced used. Scanning can be triggered from the Tools menu (for tagging the cited items) or by right-clicking a collection (for adding them to a collection). The scanner will read your AUX files and will put entries you cited in the associated LaTeX document into the current collection.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Formulas</title>
      <link>/zotero-better-bibtex/citing/formulas/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/zotero-better-bibtex/citing/formulas/index.html</guid>
      <description>Functions auth(n: number = 0, m: number = 1, creator: (&#39;author&#39; | &#39;editor&#39; | &#39;translator&#39; | &#39;collaborator&#39; | &#39;*&#39;) = &#39;*&#39;, initials: boolean = false)The first n (default: all) characters of the mth (default: first) author&#39;s last name.&#xA;parametertypennumberthe number of characters to take from the name, 0 = allmnumberselect the mth authorcreator(&#39;author&#39; | &#39;editor&#39; | &#39;translator&#39; | &#39;collaborator&#39; | &#39;*&#39;)kind of creator to select, * selects author first, and if not present, editor, translator or collaborator, in that order.initialsbooleanadd author initials authAuthEa(creator: (&#39;author&#39; | &#39;editor&#39; | &#39;translator&#39; | &#39;collaborator&#39; | &#39;*&#39;) = &#39;*&#39;, initials: boolean = false, sep: string = &#39;.&#39;)The last name of the first two authors, and &#34;.ea&#34; if there are more than two.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>